frinkiac.com 2002-06-05

# The Simpsons Sourcebook :: Privacy Policy

| | 

**The Simpsons Sourcebook - Privacy Policy**  
 _Last updated June 19, 2001_

TSS is committed to protecting your privacy and giving you the most interactive, yet secure, online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations.

 **Collecting your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before entering a contest, signing up for our newsletter, joining My TSS, or using our message board and chat room. Personal information collected by TSS often is limited to name, e-mail address, and website URL, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

If you ever want to review or update you're My TSS profile, simply visit the [**"MyTSS" Homepage**](http://www.frinky.com/miva/interactive/mytss.mv) and edit your personal information. We'll ask you to disclose your "My TSS" password so that only you can access your profile.

 **Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for three primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to news and information about the site.

The Simpsons Sourcebook will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law. In no other case will your information be disclosed.

 **Access to your Personal Information**  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the [**"My TSS" Homepage**](http://www.frinky.com/miva/interactive/mytss.mv). You can:

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us.
  * Subscribe or unsubscribe to The Simpsons Sourcebook Newsletter

 **Security of your Personal Information**  
The Simpsons Sourcebook protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your password, so do not share these with others.

 **Use of Cookies**  
To provide the most interactive experience possible, The Simpsons Sourcebook uses cookies extensively. We do not track individuals' use of the site, but we do use the cookies to personalize your experience.

When you visit the site, a cookie is placed on your computer, or is read if you have visited the site previously. The cookie is a small text file that does not contain your personal information, but does identify you to the website. We use cookies to allow us to give you the most interactive experience possible at The Simpsons Sourcebook.

 **Changes to this Statement**  
The Simpsons Sourcebook will occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy policy. For material changes to this statement, The Simpsons Sourcebook will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site. 

**Contact Information**  
The Simpsons Sourcebook welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy! Please contact us at [**john@frinky.com**](mailto:john@frinky.com)  
  
---|---
